Privacy Policy  

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Information Collection and Use**   <br>  <br>**Registration** In order to use this Web site, you must first complete the registration form and create a username and   <br>password. During registration you are required to give contact information (including email address).   <br>We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed   <br>interest.   <br>  <br>These communications are used to give you a better understanding of the site, what it offers, and how   <br>it is best utilized. As always, you have the option not to receive these types of communications (see   <br>'Opt-out'). **Uses of Information** SurveyWriter is a web-based service for conducting surveys. Any information shared with SurveyWriter   <br>during the creation of a survey is owned solely by the administrator of that survey. By the nature or how   <br>our service works, surveys need to be shared via a URL on the Internet. We provide the option to   <br>password protect your surveys if they contain sensitive content.   <br>  <br>Email addresses uploaded to the system for the purpose of sending survey invitations and email   <br>communication are owned solely by the survey administrator. We will never share any information   <br>uploaded to the system with any 3rd parties.   <br>  <br>Data collected through surveys is owned solely by the survey administrator. By default, the data is only   <br>accessible by providing a username and password and logging into the site. There is the option to   <br>share online reports via a URL from the administrative account. The survey administrator controls this   <br>option. We will never use any of the data collected. **Communications from the Site**   <br>  <br>**Ongoing Communication and Product Updates** We will occasionally send you information on product enhancements, new services, and additional   <br>instruction on utilizing our services. These communications are designed to educate our users on the   <br>services offered. Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of   <br>communications. Please see the 'Opt-out'. **Service-related Announcements** We will send you strictly service-related announcements when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if   <br>our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. Service-related   <br>emails are also sent confirming billing transactions, account upgrades, and account cancellations.   <br>  <br>Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do   <br>not wish to receive them, you have the option to cancel your account. **Information Sharing and Disclosure**   <br>  <br>**Personally Identifiable Information Sharing with Partners** If a user specifically requests a service from one of our partnering companies, their personally   <br>identifying information will be shared. The partnering company may contact them directly regarding   <br>their inquiry. Any requests of partnering companies are initiated solely by the user and it will be clearly   <br>indicated that a partnering company offers the requested service. We reserve the right to disclose your   <br>personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary   <br>to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process. **Opt-out** If you no longer wish to receive our product updates, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the   <br>instructions included in each product update email. **Cookies** A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use   <br>cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable   <br>information you submit while on our site.   <br>  <br>We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for   <br>you to navigate our site and validate that you have logged into your administrative account. A session ID   <br>cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an   <br>extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your   <br>Internet browser's 'help' file.   <br>  <br>If you reject cookies, the site will not function properly after logging in to your administrative account. **Clear Gifs** We use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by   <br>recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness   <br>of our marketing campaigns. If you would like to opt-out of these emails, please see 'Opt-out'. **Bulletin Boards**  <br>  <br>If you use a bulletin board on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information   <br>you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to   <br>send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you   <br>choose to submit in these forums. This forum is only accessible via SurveyWriter.com.  <br>  <br>**Security** We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us,   <br>both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or   <br>method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially   <br>acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. **Changes in this Privacy Statement** If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and   <br>other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it,   <br>and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy   <br>statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will   <br>notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage. **Contact Us**   <br>  <br>If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:   <br>  <br>SurveyWriter LLC, SurveyWriter.com, 3717 N Ravenswood, Suite 236 Chicago, IL, 60613,   <br>ph: 1-773-281-8490; info@SurveyWriter.com. |  |
